Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Sylvère Lotringer Projects
  - Subseries F: Notes and Fragments
    - Notes on La Chanson de Roland, Undated (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - Notes on Cliges, Undated (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - Notes - "Codex", Undated (Box 55, Folder 43)
    - Notes - communication and language, Undated (Box 55, Folder 44)
    - Notepad: "Cool Memories", Undated (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - Notes: DADA / Surrealism, Undated (Box 55, Folder 46)
    - Notes on Dante, Undated (Box 55, Folder 47)
    - List - "Dead Art", Undated (Box 55, Folder 48)
    - Notes: "Débacle Francais et exode", Undated (Box 55, Folder 49)
    - Notes - Deleuze, Undated (Box 55, Folder 50)
    - Deleuze notes, Undated (Box 55, Folder 51)
    - Notes - "Deleuze", Undated (Box 55, Folder 52)
    - Notes: "D-G Mille Plateaux", Undated (Box 55, Folder 54)
    - Notes towards a poem? - "Delicate balance", Undated (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - Notes - "Déline et panique...language", Undated (Box 55, Folder 56)
    - Derrida, de la Grammatologie - "Index de la partie", Undated (Box 55, Folder 57)
    - Notes - "Derrida, fev 1975" (Box 55, Folder 58)
    - Notes - "Discussion avec [Mauricio], Aug 3, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 59)
    - List of documentaries, Undated (Box 55, Folder 60)
    - Notes - Documents sur l'epopee" - for Swarthmore course, Undated (Box 55, Folder 61)
    - Notes: "Du Bellay and La Renaissance", Undated (Box 55, Folder 62)
    - "Evanche d'une theorie des modalites", Undated (Box 55, Folder 63)
    - Notes: Edranger, Undated (Box 55, Folder 64)
    - Notes - "Epopee Roman", Undated (Box 55, Folder 65)
    - Notes on Erec and Enide, Undated (Box 55, Folder 66)
    - Notes - "Fiches a utiliser", Undated (Box 55, Folder 67)
    - Film and book lists, Undated (Box 55, Folder 68)
    - Notes on Foucault, Undated (Box 55, Folder 69)
    - List for Frankfurt, October 1989 (Box 55, Folder 70)
    - Notes on Freud, Undated (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Notes - "Freud: Operation Structurale", Undated (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Notes - Futurama, Undated (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Notes - "Gericanult", Undated (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Notes - GM, Undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Notes on Greimas and Levi-Strauss, Undated (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Notes - Heliogatale, Undated (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Notes on Herbich, Undated (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Notes - "Histoire du Surrealisme", Undated (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Notes - Guy [Hocquengham], Undated (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Max Jacobs notes, Undated (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Kafka notes, Undated (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Notes toward interview with Julia Kristera, Undated (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Notes - Lacan, Hegel, Undated (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Notes - "Ed Lachman", Undated (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Notes on Lamartine, Undated (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Notes on LaPlanche, Undated (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Notes - "Les Liaisons Dangereuses", Undated (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Notes on Lyotard "Economie libidinale", Undated (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Notes - Lyotard "Economie libidinale", Undated (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Notes - "Mrs. Bovary and Mme. Dalloway", Undated (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Notes on Madame Bovary, Undated (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Notes - Maladie de la famille americaine, Undated (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Notes - "L'humour blanc de Mallarme", Undated (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Notes - "Manon Lescant" - for Swarthmore course, Undated (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Notes - "Marinotte", Undated (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Notes on Marivaux, Undated (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - Notes - "Marx / Minorites", Undated (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - Notes - "Michael's King Blank", Undated (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Notes on mind / symbols, Undated (Box 122, Folder 30)
    - Notes on Molloy, Undated (Box 122, Folder 31)
    - Notes - "La naissance de la monnaie", Undated (Box 122, Folder 32)
    - Joseph Nechvatal - handwritten notes from notebook, 1979 (Box 122, Folder 33)
    - Notes on Toui Negri, Undated (Box 122, Folder 34)
    - Notes - Networks, Undated (Box 122, Folder 35)
    - Notes - La nouvelle Helpoise, Undated (Box 122, Folder 36)
    - Notes on the novel, Undated (Box 122, Folder 37)
    - Notes - "Oblowicz", Undated (Box 122, Folder 38)
    - List / Notes - Paul, Undated (Box 122, Folder 39)
    - Notes - Pedophilia, Undated (Box 122, Folder 40)
    - Notes on Pere Goriot, Undated (Box 122, Folder 41)
    - Notes clipped together - "la Pharmacie de Platon; Abelard", Undated (Box 122, Folder 42)
    - Notes - production and class, Undated (Box 122, Folder 43)
    - Notes - [Proust], Undated (Box 122, Folder 44)
    - Notes - "Rene", Undated (Box 122, Folder 45)
    - Notes on Revolve, Undated (Box 122, Folder 46)
    - Notes on Ricardou, Undated (Box 122, Folder 47)
    - Notes - "M. Riffaterre sur Sade, Fourrer, Loyola", Undated (Box 122, Folder 48)
    - Notes - "Kristen Ross", c. 1999 (Box 122, Folder 49)
    - Notes - Russie, Undated (Box 122, Folder 50)
    - Notes - Saussure, Benneniste, Undated (Box 122, Folder 51)
    - Saussure / Derrida notes, Undated (Box 122, Folder 52)
    - Notes - Savoir et Pouvoir, Undated (Box 122, Folder 53)
    - Schizo notes, Undated (Box 122, Folder 54)
    - Notes Le schizo et institution, Undated (Box 122, Folder 55)
    - "Schizotexte / Interpretation of Schizophrenia", Undated (Box 122, Folder 56)
    - "Schizotexte / War of Words / Guerilla Wordfare", Undated (Box 122, Folder 57)
    - "Warmachine / Schizo Warfare", Undated (Box 122, Folder 58)
    - Notes - Sex, Undated (Box 122, Folder 59)
    - Notes - "Sexualite", Undated (Box 122, Folder 60)
    - Notes - "Struct, post-struct, beyond post-struct", Undated (Box 122, Folder 61)
    - Notes - "System and Death", Undated (Box 122, Folder 62)
    - Notes - Theorie du Roman, Undated (Box 122, Folder 63)
    - Notes and Fragments on theory, Undated (Box 122, Folder 64)
    - Notes on Todorov, Undated (Box 122, Folder 65)
    - Two annotated poems / readings - "Le tombeau d'Edgar Poe", "Le tombeau de Charles Baudelaire", Undated (Box 122, Folder 66)
    - Notes - Huber Tonka on 60's architecture, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 67)
    - Notes - Totemism, Undated (Box 122, Folder 68)
    - "Traite de nomadologie", Undated (Box 122, Folder 69)
    - Notes on Tristan et Yseut, Undated (Box 122, Folder 70)
    - Notes on Baleur, Differnace, Undated (Box 122, Folder 71)
    - Notes on Yves [Velan], Undated (Box 122, Folder 72)
    - Notebook - "Video Anonymous", Undated (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Notes on Virgil's Aeneid, Undated (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Notes - Virilio "The Accident of Art", Undated (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Notes - "Virilio Vitesse et politique", Undated (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Virilio Notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Notes on Voltaire, Undated (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Notes - "Voyage", Undated (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Notes on Virginia Woolf - Taken at the Berg Collection (NY Public Library) in preparation for MA Thesis, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Notes - [Virginia Woolf], Undated (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Notes on "Mrs. Dalloway" for dissertation, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Diverse notes on articles on Virginia Woolf, etc..., Undated (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Notes on an envelope, Undated (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - To do lists?, Undated (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Various short notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Unknown notes, interview annotations, Undated (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Various schedules and notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - notes (various), Undated (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - notes - short notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - various short notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 25)
    - Notes - Unknown, Undated (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - Unknown notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - Unknown notes found together, Undated (Box 123, Folder 28)
    - Illegible notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 29)
    - notes - unknown, Undated (Box 123, Folder 30)
    - Envelope with sketches and notes on it, Undated (Box 123, Folder 31)
    - Notes on an unknown novel, Undated (Box 123, Folder 32)
    - Notes and Logging, Undated (Box 123, Folder 33)
    - Notes / journal, Undated (Box 123, Folder 34)
    - Unknown notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 35)
    - Notes - unknown, Undated (Box 123, Folder 36)
    - Handwritten notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 37)
    - Unknown notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 38)
    - Schedule, Undated (Box 123, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 40)
- Series VI: Photographic Materials
  This series contains only photographic material that could not be linked to a larger project, or were not contained with manuscripts, subject files, or correspondence elsewhere in the archive. The series contains mostly prints, but also some slides, contact sheets and negatives.
  - Subseries A: Professional
    All photographic materials are arranged alphabetically by the photographer's name. When available, the subject's name appears in parentheses. At the end of the series, photos taken by unknown photographers can be found.
    - Ben Nomis, Amnom (Lee Breuer), undated (Box Binder A)
      1 8x10
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Berg, Bob (Chris Kraus), undated (Box Binder A)
      Item returned to donor.
    - Berg, Bob (Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Burford, Kristian, undated (Box Binder A)
      1 color slide
    - Cantrell, Emily (Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box Binder A)
      2 5x7; 1 6x9
    - Cherry, Regina (Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box Binder A)
      42 8x10; 1 5x7
    - Cohen, Ira (Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box Binder A)
      2 5x7
    - De Sana, Jimmy, undated (Box Binder A)
      5 6x9
    - Dubose, George, undated (Box Binder A)
    - Eeva-Interi (Christo), 1981 (Box Binder A)
      2 8x10
    - Elbers, Johan (Lee Breuer), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Elbers, Johan (Dounglas Dunn), 1983 (Box Binder A)
    - Ferrato, Donna, undated (Box Binder A)
      2 black and white contact sheets
    - Freccia, Ilarta (Lee Breuer), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Ganahl, Rainer (Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box Binder A)
      4 color 4x6
    - Hartnett, Elaine (Charlemagne Palestine), 1971 (Box Binder A)
    - Johnson, Craig, 1985 (Box Binder A)
      1 color 4x6
    - Kane, Jeffrey (Sylvere Lotringer), 1988 (Box Binder A)
      2 8x10; assorted photocopies
    - Kawada, Kikuji, 1965 (Box Binder A)
    - Liebowitz, Anne (Phillip Glass), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Mangolte, Babette (Richard Foreman), 1977 (Box Binder A)
    - Mangolte, Babette (Stuart Sherman), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Mangolte, Babette (Robert Wilson and Phillip Glass), 1978 (Box Binder A)
      1 7x9
    - Mangolte, Babette (Robert Wilson), undated (Box Binder A)
      1 7x9; 3 large-format negatives
    - Mangolte, Babette, 1976 (Box Binder A)
      1 7x9; 1 8x10
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, undated (Box Binder A)
      6 8x10
    - Myers, Rita (Barricade to Blue at the Kitchen), 1977 (Box Binder A)
      10 color slides
    - Rattray, David (Artaud translation projected at St Marks Poetry Project), 1980s (Box Binder A)
      140 slides
    - Robinson, Theo (Mary Overlie), 1978 (Box Binder A)
    - Rose, Sheree (Dennis Cooper), undated (Box Binder A)
      1 5x7
    - Schubert, Marcus, 1987 (Box Binder A)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Schwarz, Jeffrey (Chris Kraus), 1985 (Box Binder A)
    - [Silverthorne], Jeffrey, 1973, 1991 (Box Binder A)
    - Simon, Kate (Kathy Acker), 1986 (Box Binder A)
    - Tileston, Nathanial (Mary Overlie, et. al), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Voigt, Reinhardt, 1983 (Box Binder A)
    - Volz, Wolfgang (Christo), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Von Schaewen, Deidi (Rene Herbst), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (Susan Attington, "A Happy Death"), 1989 (Box Binder A)
    - (Douglas Dunn), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (Phillip Glass), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (Eileen Gray), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) (Chris Kraus), undated (Box Binder A)
      4 8x10
      All items returned to donor.
    - (Steve Reich), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (Reichstag), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (Nancy Reilly), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (Mallet Stevens), undated (Box Binder A)
    - (Hans Jurgen Syberborg, as Hitler), undated (Box Binder A)
    - Unknown Subjects, undated (Box Binder B)
      7 8x10; 1 7x9; 5 5x7; 5 4x6; 5 color slides; 1 black and white contact sheet
    - Notes to "Christo pictures", undated (Box Binder B)
      one large mailing envelope
  - Subseries B: Personal
    Photographic prints are arranged alphabetically by the subject's name, with unknown subjects appearing at the end. Negatives are arranged chronologically at the end of the series.
    - Cataldo, Susan, undated (Box Binder B)
      1 black and white 3x5
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris, undated (Box Binder B)
      8 color 3x5; 6 black and white 3x5
      Items returned to donor.
    - Lotringer, Mia, undated (Box Binder B)
      12 colour 3x5; 1 polaroid; 1 colour 5x7; 3 black and white 8x10
    - Lotringer, Sylvere, undated (Box Binder B)
      8 idenfication photographs; 5 colour 4x6; 2 black and white 4x6; 2 black and white 3x5; 2 black and white 5x7; 4 black and white 8x10
    - Lotringer, Sylvere and family, undated (Box Binder B)
      2 colour 5x7 6 colour 4x6 3 black and white 4x6 4 polaroids
    - Lotringer, Sylvere and friends, undated (Box Binder B)
      4 polaroids; 2 black and white 4x6; 4 colour 4x6
    - [Peraldi], Francois and [Scemama], Marion, 1988 (Box Binder B)
      3 color 4x6
    - Paris, Heidi, 1981 (Box Binder B)
      1 color 4x4
    - Wongpanlert, Thanya, undated (Box Binder B)
      3 black and white 4x6
    - Unknown Subjects, undated (Box Binder B)
      2 polaroids; 3 colour 4x6; 2 colour 3x5; 1 colour 5x7; 3 black and white 3x5; 1 black and white 4x6
    - Unknown Travel Snapshots, undated (Box Binder B)
      27 color 4x6
    - Unknown Landscapes, undated (Box Binder B)
      3 black and white 4x6; 4 color 4x4; 1 polaroid; 6 color 4x6
    - Ryndam, Montclair, August-September 1962 (Box Binder B)
      1 page of negatives
    - New Jersey Shore-South Bend, September 1962 (Box Binder B)
      2 pages of negatives
    - Florida, Christmas 1962 (Box Binder B)
    - United States, 1963 (Box Binder B)
      3 pages of negatives
    - Corsica, 1964 (Box Binder B)
    - Kingston, Erzurum [logements, toucuk, cheval], October-November 1965 (Box Binder B)
    - Van (lac de), January 1966 (Box Binder B)
    - Doqubeyazit; Istanbul, January 1966; April 1966 (Box Binder B)
    - Erzincan, Erzurum, Spring 1966 (Box Binder B)
    - Turkey, 1966-7 (Box Binder B)
    - Hashomez, Turkey/ USA, 1960s (Box Binder B)
    - Athol, undated (Box Binder B)
    - Scemama, undated (Box Binder B)
    - Wongpanlert, Thanya, undated (Box Binder B)
    - Unlabeled negatives, undated (Box Binder B)
      12 pages of negatives
- Series VII: Financial Papers
  Includes files of order forms, tax returns, invoices and receipts.
  Tax and medical files are restricted and have been removed to box 60b.
  - A-E (Box 56)
  - E-O (Box 57)
  - O-S (Box 58)
  - S-W (Box 59)
  - A-T (Box 60a)
  - RESTRICTED FILES (Taxes; Medical) (Box 60b)
- Series VIII: Clippings and Photocopies
  Contains folders of photocopies and clippings that were not labelled and could not be linked to a project elsewhere in the archive. Materials are arranged alphabetically by author's name. All miscellaneous folders are arranged chronologically at the end of the series.
  - Amery, Rex - "The Coed's Nightmare", Undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Appolinaire: Reprint of "Les Soirees de Paris", Undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - ARS Electronica Lifescience, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Art in America no. 72 - copies, Undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Antonin Artaud - "Lettres a Gemica Athanasiou" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Antonin Artaud - "Lettres a Genia Athanasiou" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Artaud photocopies, Undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Artaud to Jacques Riviere correspondence, Undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Ashby, W. Ross - "Analogie et Modeles", Undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Ayden, Erje - "The Crazy Green of Second Avenue" copy; with letter, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Baron - "De Nouveau sur Jacques Vache" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Bataille - photocopied piece of "Oeuvres Completes de G. Bataille", Undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Baudelaure, Charles - "Le peintre de la nie monerne", Undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Baudrillard - "Le trompe l'oeil" document de travail, Undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Baudrillard - from "La societe de consommation", Undated (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Baudrillard - copy of "Les abimes superficiels", Undated (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Baudrillard - photocopy of "Baudrillard: Simulations", 1983 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Beatty - "Taras Polataiko", Undated (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Bhabha, Homi - copy of essay, Undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Blanchot - "The Last Word" copy; with annotations, Undated (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - "La Boheme" - Walter Benjamin on Baudelaire, Undated (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - [Biden] copy of "Le Secret Blanche", 1994 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Bodei - photocopy of "Discorso e verita", Undated (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Bois/Krauss - "Informe", Undated (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - "Bordercrossings" copies, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Borkhuis, Charles - copy of "Dead Men's Tails", Undated (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Ken Brockman - "Your Whole Food Diet", Undated (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Buchanan article - "Symptom or Diagnosis", Undated (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Buchloh - "Richter's Facture" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Buchloh - ArtForum "Critical Reflections", 1997 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Burroughs - "The Devil's Bargain" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Burroughs letter from a published book, Undated (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Burton, Julianne - "The Camera as 'Guh': Two Decades of Film Culture and Resistance in Latin America" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Buyssens, Eric - "Origine de la linguistique synchronique de Saussure" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Cage, John - "For the Birds" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Cage, John - "John Cage at Seventy-Five", Undated (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Carrier - "Aesthete and the City", 1990 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Caws - "Exquisite Essentials" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Celine - "Hommage a Zola" copy, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Celine - "Deathman's Dance" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Cendrars, Blaise - piece from "The Novelist turned Reporter", Undated (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Clausen/Brower article - "The Confused Course of SDI", Undated (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Cohen, Sande - "Hide your commodification" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - "Collection Blance" book list, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Columbia Newspapers, Undated (Box 61, Folder 45)
  - Cotazar - "Literature et Revolution", Undated (Box 61, Folder 46)
  - Dali - piece from "Revolution Paranoiaque", Undated (Box 61, Folder 47)
  - Debord - "Le detounement", Undated (Box 61, Folder 48)
  - Debord - "Le detournement" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 49)
  - Deleuze, Gilles - excerpts from "Une vie Philosophique", Undated (Box 61, Folder 50)
  - Deleuze article in "L'autre journal", 1985 (Box 61, Folder 51)
  - "Doing It" copies, Undated (Box 61, Folder 52)
  - Dotti - "Simone Weil, la marsigliese", Undated (Box 61, Folder 53)
  - Durand, Regis - pages from "Disposition of the Voice", Undated (Box 61, Folder 54)
  - East Village Eye copies, 1980's (Box 61, Folder 55)
  - Fausto-Sterling - "How many sexes are there?", 1993 (Box 61, Folder 56)
  - Foucault - photocopy of "Interviews and other Writings", Undated (Box 61, Folder 57)
  - "Entretien avec Michel Foucault" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 58)
  - Foucault, Michel - preface copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 59)
  - Foucault - "Qu'est-ce qu'un auteur" copies, Undated (Box 61, Folder 60)
  - Foucault - "Entretien avec Michel Foucault", Undated (Box 61, Folder 61)
  - Gibson - "Johnny Mnemonic", Undated (Box 61, Folder 62)
  - Gille, Didier and Stengers, Isabelle - "Body Fluids", Undated (Box 61, Folder 63)
  - Giribone - Table of Contents for "La Couleur des Idees", Undated (Box 61, Folder 64)
  - Gluck - "Jack the Modernist" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 65)
  - Goddard - "France / Tour / Detour / Deux / Enfants", Undated (Box 61, Folder 66)
  - Goldfarb, Alvin - "Theatrical activities in Nazi concentration camps" photocopy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 67)
  - Guillerme, Jacques - "The Idea of Architectural Language: a Critical Inquiry"; with add attached, Undated (Box 61, Folder 68)
  - Haddad, G. - "Transmission et Rites Alimentaires" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 69)
  - Huelsenbeck - copy of poem "L'amiral cherche une maison a louer", Undated (Box 61, Folder 70)
  - Jameson - "Postmodernism" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 71)
  - Jameson - "Postmodernism" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 72)
  - Jameson, Fredric - Interview in article, Undated (Box 61, Folder 73)
  - Jayet - "Les Cahiers d'Aimable Jayet" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 74)
  - Gradiro - "Jensen's Gradiro" in German, Undated (Box 61, Folder 75)
  - Julien, Dominique - "Fiat Lux" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 76)
  - Kaijima Foundation for the arts, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 77)
  - Kester - "The Rise and Fall of Baudrillard" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 78)
  - Kosko - "Fuzzy Thinking" copies, Undated (Box 61, Folder 79)
  - Kosuth, Joseph - "Five Recent Details" copies, Undated (Box 61, Folder 80)
  - Kotz - "Interrogating the boundaries of women's art" copy, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 81)
  - Kunst - Article on Virilio (in German), Undated (Box 61, Folder 82)
  - Kuspit - "Louise Bourgeois", Undated (Box 61, Folder 83)
  - Lacan and Vincennes - "Lacan", Undated (Box 61, Folder 84)
  - Leclaire, Serge, Undated (Box 61, Folder 85)
  - Lejeune, Philippe - "Le pacte autobiographique" copy, Undated (Box 61, Folder 86)
  - Les Lettres Française, Undated (Box 61, Folder 87)
  - L'Étrave - Prope Doutique - Paris Lettre, undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Lingis "The Society of Dismembered Body Parts" copy, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Livingston, Marco on Koons, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Le Livres des Morts Tibétain, undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Lotringer interview with Müller and Werkstatt Berlin flyer, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Lotringer/During interview - article on "French Theory", undated (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Lotringer essay on Guattari "No Comment", undated (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Lotringer "Interview with Brendan Behan, Dublin 1961 with [GPY] article in Les Lettres Françaises", undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Lotringer interview with Brendan Behan (for Seamus Dean) - "L'Homme Maigre", undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Lotringer - Brendan Behan Interviews, undated (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Lotringer - "Editorial, undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Lotringer - "Third Wave: Art and the Commodification of Theory" copy, undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Lotringer - "Agents de l'étranger" copy (history of Semiotext(e) in French), undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Lotringer - Two interviews with French publishers for student paper PARIS - Lettres #3 (Sorbonne), 1960 January (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Lotringer interview with Heiner Müller in Liberation, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - "Sylvère Lotringer: The Diaghilev of Deconstruction" by Andrew Olds, undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Lotringer - "The Game of the Name", undated (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Lotringer - "The Salut par les Juifs", undated (Box 62, Folder 18)